<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Authors: 4144, Reid
Copyright (C) 2012 Evol Online -->
<quests>
    <var id="0">
        <quest name="Julia" group="Ship" incomplete="2" complete="4">
            <name>Abide by the Rules</name>
            <text>Before resuming your adventure and exploration, you will need to register on the boarding list of the ship, and to sign its rules.</text>
        </quest>
        <quest name="Julia" group="Ship" incomplete="1" complete="1">
            <name>Abide by the rules</name>
            <text>Rules:</text>
            <text>1. Do not bot. This means are not allowed to run any automated or use keyboard tricks. Any away from keyboard activity will be considered as botting. This does not include standing still.</text>
            <text>2. Do not spam. This also concerns trade spam.</text>
            <text>3. Do not multibox. This mean you cannot have more than one active character logged in at a time. You are not allowed to use more than one active client at a time to attack in groups.</text>
            <text>4. Do not trashtalk, beg or use rude language in your character name or in the chat, at the exception of roleplay purposes.</text>
            <text>5. Do not speak any other language other than English in the public areas. You are free to speak any language you want in private chats, or when alone with friends.</text>
            <text>6. Follow the social convention listed on the RFC1855 article.</text>
        </quest>
    </var>
    <var id="1">
        <quest name="Magic Arpan" group="Ship" incomplete="0" complete="1">
            <name>Speaking with Magic Arpan</name>
            <text>Magic Arpan is waiting for you. Go speak with him.</text>
            <text>To speak to an NPC, click on him with your mouse or select him with then N key and then start to chat with him with the T key.</text>
        </quest>
        <quest name="Magic Arpan" group="Ship" incomplete="1" complete="2">
            <name>Opening the Chest</name>
            <text>You need to open the chest and to take the clothes from it.</text>
            <text>To perform this action, click on the chest with your mouse or select it with the N key and then interact with it using the T key.</text>
        </quest>
        <quest name="Magic Arpan" group="Ship" incomplete="2" complete="3">
            <name>Equip an Item</name>
            <text>Open your inventory by using the F3 key or use your mouse to select it in the menu of your client.</text>
            <text>Once your inventory is open, you may equip the item by selecting it and clicking 'Equip'. Alternately, you can take off an equipment by clicking on 'Unequip'.</text>
            <text>Some items perform different effects. Some will heal you, some can be used as weapons or armors, and others can be sold for gold.</text>
        </quest>
    </var>
    <var id="3">
        <quest name="Peter" group="Ship" incomplete="6" complete="2">
            <name>Ratto Extermination</name>
            <text>Peter needs your help to clean the bottom of the ship from some Rattos. Speak with him when you will have some time to help him.</text>
        </quest>
        <quest name="Peter" group="Ship" incomplete="2" complete="5">
            <name>Ratto Extermination</name>
            <text>Cleaning the bottom of the ship is a hard work, but Peter is offering you some gold for it.</text>
            <text></text>
            <text>Difficulty: ✭✩✩✩✩✩</text>
            <text>Rewards: 500GP, 100EXP.</text>
        </quest>
        <quest name="Peter" group="Ship" incomplete="1" complete="3">
            <name>Free Cave Washer</name>
            <text>Peter asked you to empty freely the bottom of the ship.</text>
            <text>It seems that you should again ask him this task, he may got something else to offer you...</text>
            <text></text>
            <text>Difficulty: ✭✩✩✩✩✩</text>
            <text>Reward: 0GP, 0EXP.</text>
        </quest>
        <quest name="Peter" group="Ship" incomplete="3" complete="4">
            <name>Free Cave Washer</name>
            <text>Ask him about a reward for this task.</text>
        </quest>
    </var>
    <var id="4">
        <quest name="Nard" group="Ship" incomplete="1" complete="2">
            <name>Nard</name>
            <text></text>
        </quest>
    </var>
    <var id="8">
        <quest name="Darlin" group="Ship" incomplete="1" complete="2">
            <name>Treasure's Glints</name>
            <text>A weird light reflection is annoying Darlin. He asked you to go and check what this could be.</text>
            <text>The light comes from the top of a cliff, west of the island. A road seems to go there.</text>
            <text></text>
            <text>Coordinates: 000-1 83,70</text>
            <text>Difficulty: ✩✩✩✩✩✩</text>
            <text>Rewards: Unknown.</text>
        </quest>
        <quest name="Darlin" group="Ship" incomplete="2" complete="3">
            <name>Treasure's Glints</name>
            <text>The sailor was right. The light was the glint of the sun on a treasure chest.</text>
            <text>Darlin seems to be waiting for you. You should tell him about light.</text>
            <text></text>
            <text>Coordinates: 000-1 83,70</text>
            <text>Difficulty: ✩✩✩✩✩✩</text>
            <text>Rewards: 400GP, 0EXP, Old Book.</text>
        </quest>
    </var>
</quests>
