<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Authors: 4144, Reid
Copyright (C) 2012 Evol Online -->
<quests>
    <var id="0">
        <quest name="Julia" group="Ship" incomplete="2" complete="4">
            <name>Abide by the rules</name>
            <text>Before to continue your adventure and exploration, you'll need to register yourself on the list of the ship, and to sign the rules list.</text>
        </quest>
        <quest name="Julia" group="Ship" incomplete="1" complete="1">
            <name>Abide by the rules</name>
            <text>Rules:</text>
            <text>1. Do not bot, this means that you won't run any automated tasks (Also included keyboard tricks). Any away from keyboard activity is considered botting does not include standing still.</text>
            <text>2. Do not spam. (includes trade spam)</text>
            <text>3. Do not multibox, this mean that you cannot have more than one active character logged in or any other active clients used for attacking in group.</text>
            <text>4. Don't trashtalk, beg or use rude language in your character name and in the chat, at the exception of roleplay purposes.</text>
            <text>5. Don't speak any other language other than English in the public areas. You are free to speak any language you want in private chats and when alone with groups of friends.</text>
            <text>6. Follow the social convention listed on the RFC1855.</text>
        </quest>
    </var>
    <var id="1">
        <quest name="Peter" group="Ship" incomplete="6" complete="2">
            <name>Ratto Exterminator</name>
            <text>Peter need your help to clean the bottom of the ship from some Ratto. Speak with him when you'll got some time.</text>
        </quest>
        <quest name="Peter" group="Ship" incomplete="2" complete="5">
            <name>Ratto Exterminator</name>
            <text>Cleaning the bottom of the ship is a hard work, but Peter is offering you some gold against it.</text>
            <text></text>
            <text>Difficulty: ✭✩✩✩✩✩</text>
            <text>Reward: 500GP and 100xp.</text>
        </quest>
        <quest name="Peter" group="Ship" incomplete="1" complete="3">
            <name>Free Cave Washer</name>
            <text>Peter asked you to empty freely the bottom of the ship.</text>
            <text>It seems that you should again ask him this task, he may got something else to offer you...</text>
            <text></text>
            <text>Difficulty: ✭✩✩✩✩✩</text>
            <text>Reward: 0GP.</text>
        </quest>
        <quest name="Peter" group="Ship" incomplete="3" complete="4">
            <name>Free Cave Washer</name>
            <text>Ask about a reward for this task.</text>
        </quest>
    </var>
    <var id="3">
        <quest name="Magic Arpan" group="Ship" incomplete="0" complete="1">
            <name>Speak with Magic Arpan</name>
            <text>Magic Arpan is waiting you, speak with him.</text>
            <text>To speak with a NPC, click on him with your mouse, or select him with your N key, you can then start to chat with him with the T key.</text>
        </quest>
        <quest name="Magic Arpan" group="Ship" incomplete="1" complete="2">
            <name>Open the Chest</name>
            <text>You need to open the Chest, and to take the clothes from this.</text>
            <text>To perform this action, click on the Chest with your mouse, or select it with your N key, you can then start to chat with him with the T key.</text>
        </quest>
        <quest name="Magic Arpan" group="Ship" incomplete="2" complete="3">
            <name>Equip an item</name>
            <text>Open your inventory by using the F3 key or use your mouse to select it in the menu of your client.</text>
            <text>Once you're inside of your inventory, you may equip the item by selecting it and clicking 'Equip'. Alternately, you can unequip an item by selecting 'unequip' to remove it. </text>
            <text>Certain items perform different effects. Some will heal you, some you may use as weapons or armor, and some can be sold for gold.</text>
        </quest>
    </var>
    <var id="4">
        <quest name="Nard" group="Ship" incomplete="1" complete="2">
            <name>Nard</name>
            <text></text>
        </quest>
    </var>
</quests>
